New Boston, 911. What's your emergency?
I need an ambulance
'cause I started having my baby.
Stay on the line.
I'm gonna get you to LifeNet.
-I have a trooper behind me.
-Stay on the line.
It's gonna be okay. Stay on the line.
Emergency.
I just need an ambulance to get to Idabel.
She's gone into labor.
She has a state trooper behind her.
Okay.
-Hurry! Please!
-Is the trooper with her?
Yeah, he was, uh,
pulling her over as she called.
Ma'am, are you still here with me?
-What's wrong, ma'am?
-I had my baby.
And I'm trying to get to I-Idabel Hospital
where my husband--
-Idabel?
-Yeah, my husband's up there.
Need LifeNet out, uh, to my location.
Lady in this vehicle
who appeared to just have a baby.
She was carrying the baby in her lap.
Umbilical cord is still attached.
She's not breathing.
The baby's not breathing.
She's doing CPR on the baby right now.
Can you just put me in your car
and drive us so we're not sitting?
Please, I'm begging you.
There's nothing I can do.
You're gonna need EMS.
I'm fine, if you'll just get us there
as quick as possible.
Thank you. Uh, LifeNet's already on scene.
-You just gave birth?
-Turn around and sit down.
How old you say you was?
-27.
-27?
-I think I was born in '92.
-Okay.
So you was-- You was on your way
to Idabel to-- to have the baby?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Okay.
Just relax, darling.
Do not let her out that door.
-I'm gonna need--
-Getting real, real jumpy in there.
So she shows no signs…
You won't-- You can't check
for hemorrhaging?
She should be hemorrhaging by now.
She's in there.
She refuses to have a vaginal check
to make sure she's not hemorrhaging.
They've done ultrasound and HCG,
and it doesn't show
that she's been pregnant.
They have the placenta.
-Where is she?
-She is in the room.
-You're not letting her leave?
-No.
-Can I help you?
-This is…
-This is a big deal.
-Yeah.
Hey, there.
What's your name?
Taylor Parker.
Taylor. Hey.
My name is Chad Dansby. I'm a…
I'm an OSBI agent up here,
and I heard you brought your baby in.
Yes, sir.
Did you give birth
on the side of the road or something?
-Yes, sir.
-Oh, okay.
Where was that? Here? In McCurtain County?
No, it was in De Kalb.
De Kalb. Down in Texas?
-Yes, sir.
-Oh, okay.
Did I do something wrong
for them bringing me over here?
So you-- you gave birth to this child?
Yes. I--
We're-- We're just making sure, okay?
If there's anything you need
to talk to us about, you can.
I don't know what everybody
wants me to talk about.
I'm just trying to figure out
where this baby came from.
I just told y'all what happened.
Okay.
What's the doctor gonna find
when he comes in and checks you?
Is he gonna find you just gave birth?
-I--
-They can tell.
When he looks, he can tell
in about a second
if you gave birth or not.
O-- Okay.
So is he gonna find
that you gave birth this morning?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-Let's see.
-So we'll jump out.
Sit you up.
All right, well, let me have
them sit you up there
where I can see what I'm doing.
I didn't-- It doesn't look
like she had a baby.
-It doesn't?
-No.
Okay.
Does not look
like she had a baby down there.
Where'd this baby come from?
It's mine!
Can't be.
Who is Taylor?
What happened
to the car that she gave you?
Was she starting to look pregnant ever?
Mount Pleasant Police Department.
I just received a caller,
and he said
there is a bomb in the hospital.
Okay, so a male subject called
and said there was a bomb in the hospital?
Yes, sir. He said…
New Boston, 911. What's your emergency?
Ma'am. Ma'am?
Help me. My daughter's been murdered.
Okay, where are you located at?
At…  Street.
-In New Boston?
-Yeah.
What happened?
I don't know. Somebody got in her house.
-She's dead!
-Okay.
She's dead!
-What's wrong, ma'am?
-I had my baby.
And I'm trying to get to Idabel Hospital
where my husband--
-Idabel?
-Yeah, my husband's up there.
He was delivering hogs
right outside of Idabel.
That's why I was trying to get to him.
Can you call my husband?
-Yes.
-How old's the baby, ma'am?
The baby's only, like,
maybe 35 minutes old.
She was flying down the road.
You stopped her or what?
She was driving down the road,
passing on the shoulder.
She had her hazards on.
She ran over a bird.
It's still on-- uh, in the grille here.
Did a name come back on that 27?
Her name's Taylor.
I don't have her last name.
Uh, the car is r-- registered
to Wade Griffin.
I think he's already
in Oklahoma, uh, working.
-Hello?
-Where you at?
I'm trying-- I'm trying
to get these, um, these hogs moved.
What's up?
We're-- We're going to the hospital.
We're going to Titus.
All right, well,
let me finish what I'm doing.
I'll call you right back.
Okay?
All right. Bye.
So you was-- you was on your way
to Idabel to have the baby?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Okay. It's all right.
Just relax, darling.
We need to know
whether the baby's in there or not.
'Cause there's an awful lot
of blood everywhere.
The only way we can
know that is to-- is to roll her over.
Okay.
-There's no baby in there.
-No.
No. There's no baby in there.
So she was pregnant?
Yes, 36 weeks.
She's in there.
She refuses to have a vaginal check
to make sure she's not hemorrhaging.
They've done an ultrasound and HCG,
and it doesn't show
that she's been pregnant.
They have the placenta.
-Where is she?
-She is in the room.
-You're not letting her leave?
-No.
-Can I help you?
-This is…
-This is a big deal.
-Yeah.
If there's anything
you need to talk to us about, you can.
I don't know what everybody
wants me to talk about.
You gave birth to this child?
Yes. I--
We're just making sure.
Did I do something wrong
for them bringing me over here?
What did you have? A boy or a girl?
-A girl.
-A girl. Okay.
Picked out a name yet?
Clancy Gaile.
-Clancy Gaile.
-Hi.
-All right.
Let's see.
Sit you up.
All right. Well, let me have
them sit you up there
where I can see what I'm doing.
So it surely doesn't look
like a baby came out of there.
I didn't-- It doesn't look
like she had a baby.
-It doesn't?
-No.
Okay.
Does not look
like she had a baby down there.
Hey, Taylor. So what happened?
Nothing happened.
You didn't give birth.
We're past all this nonsense
about "I wasn't there."
"I didn't kill nobody."
We're past all of that.
We know it. We know you did it.
The bottom line is these cases
are actually pretty simple.
Murder cases are pretty simple.
You have a who, what,
when, where, and why.
Watch your toes.
Under no circumstance
is she to have her phone or purse.
-Okay. Okay.
-All right?
She's to be, uh… separated
from her boyfriend who's down there.
You know the baby's dead?
-Yeah, I heard.
-Okay.
Tell me about the-- your house.
You had a nursery set up at the house?
Yeah, we bought a crib
and clothes and diapers.
Who bought all that?
Me and Wade.
Okay. Was he excited
about the baby coming?
No.
Why not?
He's never been excited about it.
Can I please go to the bathroom?